

Santosh Shah

Date of birth: 11/03/1998 | **Nationality:** Nepalese | **Gender:** Male |

(+977) 9812008477 | shahnema77@gmail.com

https://myportfolio-88677.web.app/ 45700, Jaleshwar, Mahottari, Nepal

About me:

Hey, Thanks for viewing my resume!

I am Santosh Shah, I have completed my +2 College degree (intermediate) this year. I have good experience as a Web developer and IT Support/Solutions and also have experience in an Electronic manufacturing company as (ManufacutringTrainer/Leader), I am a fast learner with hard working and honest person and I am very loyal to my work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 - 2021 - Penang, Malaysia

HR IT TECHNICIAN SUPPORT/MANUFACTURING TRAINER – JABIL INC. (ELECTRONICS MANUFACTURING COMPANY)

Jabil company is an electronics manufacturing and provides chain and logistic services and assembling Parts for companies such as Tesla, cisco, Micron, Arista, etc..., i was working as HR manufacturing trainer Support / (IT) Technician support and my task was as below:

- Brief the new hire workers related skills such as (Basic computer Hardware/Software, and manufacturing machine programs/software)
- Maintaining computers/ Networks at HR office/Production area and also solving Networking connectivity/Computer program errors or issues
- Assists Senior IT technician at Production (manufacturing)area for maintaining computer hardware/ software/ Networking Troubleshooting
- $^\circ$ Assists senior IT technician during new production area expands or add new lines and my task is there check computer network (LAN/WAN) connectivity to maintain
- Help HR team for making an online project (paperless) online test/learning website for the manufacturing workers E-learning platform

2021 - CURRENT - Kathmandu, Nepal

WEB DEVELOPER - FREELANCER

I am Working as a web developer and have provided a lot of services as well mention below:

- design and establish user-friendly websites and optimized check-out pages
- establish interactive and dynamic websites Maintain websites
- Transformed static website to dynamic with backend interface
- build a budget E-commerce website with a full front-end and back-end interface
- diagnosed and troubleshoot different websites of the company's critical clients by deploying updated knowledge of the modern technologies and techniques in the industry

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2021 - CURRENT - Patna, India

HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE (+2) – Chanakya National Law University Campus

Address Nyaya Nagar, Mithapur Patna 800001 Bihar India, Patna, India | Website https://cnlu.ac.in/

Address Lalbandi, Sarlahi (Nepal), Sarlahi, Nepal

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

HTML,CSS,SASS | Javascript | React,React Native | C/C++ | Material Angular | AZ-303 Certification | AWS | CCNA 200-301 | Microsoft Office - All | node-JS | python | SQL/MYSQL